

# CONTACT

- 077 699 5019
- khaiductam@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/vinhlam94
- Hoc Mon, HO CHI MINH city, VIETNAM

### SKILLS

- Window
- Linux
- System Monitoring
- Network infrastructure
- Python, Develop
- Office Support
- WM Ware
- Teamwork
- Communication
- Research
- English

### EDUCATION

#### LY TU TRONG COLLEGE

Information Technology 2012 – 2015

### NHAT NGHE EDUCATION JSC MCSA 2104

### NHAT NGHE EDUCATION JSC CCNA 2015

# HUỲNH LÂM QUANG VINH

## **ABOUT ME**

I have 7 years of experience in managing enterprise network systems, providing user support, IT equipment management, and network system deployment. I have worked in multiple companies with diverse work environments, which has developed my ability to learn independently and adapt well to different work environments.

# EXPERIENCE

# **VCCORP CORPORATION | IT Helpdesk**

AUG 2021 - PRESENT

- Support in the office, monitor network system, Wi-Fi, conference room equipment, cameras, and timekeeping devices.
- Manage the entire office switch system, from core switches to access switches, and servers.
- Configure and implement servers. Implement office network infrastructure. Research new applications to enhance work performance and ensure system stability. Establish a lab for studying network models.
- Managing vCenter and VM ESXi systems.
- Operating a monitoring system consisting of Grafana, Prometheus, LibreNMS, and Centreon.
- Managing DNS, DHCP systems, Gateway Fortinet.

# FE CREDIT FINANCIAL COMPANY | IT Support Specialist

NOV 2018 - AUG 2021

- Support users inside/outside about software, hardware for laptops, desktops and printers.
- Coordinate with other teams whenever necessary to solve technical, or network issues.
- Install and configure desktops/laptops and applications.
- Diagnose hardware/software problems and provide solution.

## MOBILE WORLD JSC | IT Helpdesk

OCT 2015 - NOV 2018

- Monitor and maintain the local computer systems, camera systems, and networks (firewall, switch, Wi-Fi...)
- Install and configure desktops/laptops and applications.
- Diagnose hardware/software problems and provide solutions.
- Set up and configure new shops Implement projects of the company.